Теперь у нас есть хорошя сцена но я думаю мы можем лучше.
В движке есть интересные вещи
и одну из них я вам сейчас покажу.
We'll start by learning the basics of Unreal Engine, how to maneuver throughout the viewport and manipulate
objects.
Well, then create a completely blank open world map and add lighting and sky and learn how these objects
work with each other.
We'll create a beautiful atmosphere for our world with two sons, and you're encouraged to customize
your sky, to get it to look exactly how you want.
We then learn how to add a landscape to our open world and sculpt hills and valleys and mountains,
then apply materials to get different biomes and environments.
With landscape painting, we'll learn the foliage editor and get realistic mega scan assets for free
from Pixel Bridge, a massive library of assets built into the engine.
And we'll add rocks, trees, grass and growth to create a beautiful forest in the middle of our open
world desert.
After world building, I teach you the basics of vectors and math for video games.